Announcer thing, Announcer
thing, Announcer thing!
What?
You know how we were having
trouble with the jigsaw puzzle?
Yeah?
Well, we solved it, and so we're free!
That's good to know.
Did you know I've never been
voted for to be eliminated?
Wow! Coolio!
I'm the only Squishy Cherry who's like that.
The only other people who haven't been voted for are
Leafy,
Teardrop,
Rocky, and...
Snowball!
Crudliously? Snowball's never been voted for?
But he's a jerk.
Yeah, well, you know...
Oh! You know, I've been voted for in four episodes.
No one else has been.
Well, that's okay because you're still here!
Now for my vote status!
I-
I've only been voted once, by Artofliving123,
even though I shouldn't have been.
Really, Bubble?
You know, I think your voice has changed.
WAAAH! You're not Bubble!
No, I'm not.
You murdered her!
Yeah, well, that is true.
♪ [INTRO PLAYS] ♪
Subtitles: Daniel Adam Valle
Anyway, since there was no voting
last time, there is no Cake at Stake.
So, we can get right to the contest.
It's a relay race.
- STUMP!
- OW!
Hold on a second! There's something that's unfair!
My team has many more members than the other team.
So, if everyone goes once, we'll take much LONGER!
OK, I'll fix that.
Four people of the Cherry team will go twice.
Not fair! We'll TIRE by the second time through!
Well then, no one goes twice,
but on the Grapes, only five of the
people go, so four people don't go.
Not fair! THEY get to choose
the best players but WE can't!
Grr. Then what do you suggest the rules to be?
How about this?
Like you just said, five on each team go,
but YOU randomly choose which
five Grapes participate in the race!
Hm, I guess that sounds fair enough to me.
Grapes, here's a nine-slice wheel.
Each person has one slice.
The first five people chosen by
this wheel participate in the race.
So, someone give it a whirl.
Since I'm the strongest one here by FAAAR,
it better land on ME!
Hi, weirdos! Here's another prank.
But this one involves Ice Cube instead of Bubble.
Just take an Ice Cube Recovery Center and, like,
just carry it over to the edge of a cliff...
maybe...with a tree...
Yeah, yeah. With a tree. Definitely, yeah.
That's mandatory.
And attach a spring from the tree
to the Ice Cube Recovery Center,
and then...melt...Ice Cube.
[WHISPERING]
Melting her kills her, right?
???
Yeaaah.
BLOCKY
Okay, good.
[NORMAL] Ice Cube is recreated
in the Ice Cube Recovery Center.
She'll, like, weigh it down, and...
the Ice Cube Recovery Center
will tilt down off the cliff,
and Ice Cube will fall out, and she'll...
crash at the bottom of the...cliff!
And Ice Cube is recreated in
the Ice Cube Recovery Center.
She'll, like, weigh it down, and the Ice Cube
Recovery Center will tilt down off the cliff.
Cycle repeats!
Yeah, isn't that cool?
Pretty funny?
This program was brought to you
by Blocky's Funny Doings International.
Oh, no.
You'd BETTER be a good runner!
Are you?
Yeah, WATCH! Here we go.
Wow, you're such a fast runner!
Thank you, wise Ice Cube!
Wow, you're such a slow runner!
No thank you, dumb Coiny!
Spin again.
Bleh!
Um, who's on that slice?
I ain't scraping that off!
Well, process of elimination!
There's SB, Leafy, Rocky, me,
Teardrop, Tennis Ball, and Coiny.
Firey's been chosen, so it's Ice Cube!
Oh, great. A weak, ARMLESS one.
Ha-ha, HA! Oh, that's just great! A-ha!
Two spots left.
There's only one more person
participating in this race.
If it isn't ME, we are DEAD!
NOOOOOOOOOOOOO!
[SPED UP]
Ha-ha! You didn't make the team!
OW!
So, yes. You five will compete.
You four won't.
So, the rules are simple.
Just run to the tree and back.
Oh! Also, in this episode,
no one's getting sent to the TLC.
Again, for, like, the second time?
I liked it when there was elimination.
It adds anticipation and self-preservation!
Don't worry. Next episode,
two people will be eliminated.
But I'll get to that later.
So, nothing happens to the losers.
The winners get a prize.
Which IS...?
You'll find out later.
GRRRRRRR!
But there is one catch.
While running, you must carry
the person who will run the race after you.
The last person in line doesn't carry anyone.
Yeah! I don't have to carry anyone!
Yeah! I only have to carry Bubble!
I have to carry Match, and
I know she's gaining weight!
ANNOUNCER: Go.
Faster, Eraser faster!
- AAAWAAAAHHH!
- Why are you screaming, Ice Cube?
- Are you melting?
Get on, Pencil!
She's pretty much gone.
The Ice Cube Recovery Center won't
start until she's completely melted!
Well, what are you waiting for? Melt, Firey!
Here comes the tree!
Icy, because you have no arms, I'll have to sit on you.
Go, go, go!
We're here!
AAAAAAHHHHH!
Pencil, I'm not fat, am I?
I was just JK kidding, Match!
Oh, okay then.
Back on!
Hey, they lapped us!
Release!
Hey, Golf Ball.
Oh, WOW, you're HEAVY!
Match, not so hard! You'll pop me!
Uh-oh! Where's the BRC?
I'm coming, Match!
Wow, you're HEAVY!
You already said that!
- BUBBLE: I'm getting there! Coming!
- OMT, she'd better get here soon.
- BUBBLE: Almost there! A little bit more!
BUBBLE:
Where am I? I don't know where I am.
Ugh!
Hm!
Bleh!
Remember, Match: not too hard!
O-kay!
[GRAPES COMMAND]
Run, Rocky! RUN!
Grr!
[GRAPES COMMAND]
- Go, go!
- Run, Rocky! RUN!
GRR!!!
Yeah, we won!
Yeah!
We won? That's a relief.
I wasn't expecting we'd win, but I'm glad we DID!
Thanks a lot, Bubble.
It's your fault we lost!
So, Grapes, do you want to know your prize?
YEAAAH!
You win an eliminated player onto your team.
Uh, do we get to choose WHICH player?
No, you do not. But voters, you do.
You can vote an eliminated player back into the game.
There's Flower-
You'd BETTER vote me, or-or I'll CRUSH you!
ANNOUNCER:
Spongy-
Heeelllllooo.
ANNOUNCER:
Blocky-
Vote for me! I've got an edge!
Well, twelve edges, actually.
ANNOUNCER:
Woody-
Ehhh....ahhh...
ANNOUNCER:
Pin-
You need a heroic leader like ME!
ANNOUNCER:
and Needy.
DON'T call me Needy!
♪ [Kenet & Raz - Unreal Super Hero 3] ♪